Billions In Change

Change starts with one. It starts with you.

Privacy Policy
==============

EFFECTIVE DATE: October 20, 2015

Any information that you provide of a confidential personal nature or otherwise through this website (“**Site**“) will be handled in accordance with the following Privacy Policy (“**Policy**“). Your use of the Site is contingent upon your acceptance of the Terms and Conditions of this Site as well as the guidelines of this Policy. If you do not accept the terms of this Policy, you may not use the Site.

##### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

_Authorization._ You understand and agree that Billions in Change, LLC and its authorized business partners, affiliates, subsidiaries, and agents (collectively, “**Billions in Change**“, “us” or “we”) may collect, maintain, and process information provided by you, on and through the Site. You represent and warrant that you have permission to share any information you elect to provide Billions in Change and that such information is accurate, current, non-misleading, consistent, and relevant for the purpose for which you are providing information.

_Example of Use._ As an example of the type of information we collect and use, we require you to provide a name, valid email, address, and other information as part of the registering an account on the Site or the Contact Us submission process. We may use such information to communicate with you regarding our products and services and those of our subsidiaries, affiliates, and parent companies and any of their related businesses. You may elect to opt-out from receiving materials from us by following the instructions found below in the Opt-out section.

_Age Restrictions._ Billions in Change does not knowingly market to, solicit or collect data from persons under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, we ask that you do not to use this Site. While we cannot take any special action to learn your age, if we learn that you are under 18 years of age, we will not maintain or use any personally identifiable information about you. If you believe your minor-child has provided personally identifiable information to us, please contact us so we can allow you the opportunity to review and delete such information.

_Passive Collection._ We may record and collect information about how you use the Site. This data may include your language, type of browser, operating system, Internet Service Provider, Internet protocol address, access times, referring website addresses, etc. We may monitor, use, and share such data to measure the Site’s performance, activity, and improve the Site’s design and functionality. As with many Internet sites, we may use “cookies” or “web beacons” to, among other things, enhance the functionality of the Site and to make transactions and other activities through the Site more convenient and efficient for visitors. A “cookie” is a file stored locally on a user’s computer. Most Internet browsers include preference settings that allow users to be notified and control whether cookies are transferred to their computers.

##### WHEN AND WITH WHOM WE MAY SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

_Use of Information Collected._ Billions in Change will share your personal information with third-party companies for purposes such as responding to your inquires, providing you the requested services, or other business purposes. To the extent Billions in Change hires other companies to provide limited services on its behalf, we will provide those companies with your information to provide us with such services.

_Sale or Transfer._ In the event of the sale of Billions in Change, or in the event of a transfer of our assets, Site or operations, Billions in Change may disclose or transfer your personal information in connection with such transaction.

_Disclosure pursuant to law._ We will also disclose your personal information, without notice, when required to do so to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Billions in Change or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Billions in Change; and, (c) protect the personal safety of users of Billions in Change, its websites, or the public.

_Your Consent to Share._ By providing any personal information to us, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the transfer of such personal information and the collection and processing of such personal information. Your personal information will be stored and processed on computers in the United States. The laws on holding personal information in the United States may vary and be less stringent than laws of your state. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to hold and transmit your personal information in a safe, confidential, and secure environment. If you object to your personal information being transferred or used in this manner, do not register with or use the Site.

##### ONLINE TRACKING

At this time, this Site does not support Do-Not-Track signals.

##### OPT-OUT CHOICES

To “opt-out” of (1) any consents previously given to us, (2) receiving communications from us, or (3) having personal information disclosed to third parties, send an e-mail to [billionsinchange@billionsinchange.com](mailto:billionsinchange@billionsinchange.com). Notwithstanding this right to request to cease receiving communications from us and to have us not share personal information with third parties, we retain the right to collect, maintain and process information provided by and collected about you on and through the Site, and disclose such information to comply with its reasonable business and legal obligations.

##### ACCESS TO PERSONAL INFORMATION

To the extent that you may provide personal information to us on or through the Site, we will allow reasonable access to, and review of, such information, where such information is readily available, upon proper verification and authentication of the person (author) seeking such access and review. You may request review and revisions to your personal information through the [billionsinchange@billionsinchange.com](mailto:billionsinchange@billionsinchange.com) email address. After receipt of verification, we will change or delete your personal information at your request.

##### CONSENT TO PROCESSING

By using or providing information to the Site, you understand and unambiguously consent to the collection, processing, sharing, and use of such information in the United States for the purposes set forth in this Policy.

##### SECURITY

Due to the nature of the Internet, we cannot and do not guarantee that communications with the Site will be free from unauthorized access.

##### JOB APPLICANTS

Billions in Change only collects the personal information that you voluntarily provide, which may include your name, address, telephone number, email address, employment history, education history, expected income, eligibility to work in the U.S., and any other information you share. We will use that information for the purpose for which such information was provided. We do not request, nor should you provide, sensitive data such as your social security number, driver’s license number, bank account information, credit card information, passwords, or date of birth. Your online application, resume, and/or cover letter may be retained for future reference, or as required by law. We may disclose your application data to third party service providers who perform services for or on behalf of Billions in Change.

##### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Billions in Change reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time by updating this posting, and your use of this Website after such change signifies your acceptance of the changed terms. Periodically check these terms for revisions.

##### CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have questions or concerns about your privacy when using the Site, contact Billions in Change by email at [billionsinchange@billionsinchange.com](mailto:billionsinchange@billionsinchange.com).

Share this page

COMPANY

©2024 Classic Films, LLC. All Rights Reserved.

Footer Bottom Menu
